(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Wait... This is good... I did it...
I infiltrated this place...
Success!
大成功じゃ！
Great success!
あ、みんなに見られた。
Ah, everyone saw me.
I can't believe you guys were watching me this whole time!
No!
To be honest... mmm, I did feel... mmm, I did feel eyes on me...
But... mmm... I... I knew you guys were watching, it's okay.
Anyways, it's not the time to be talking about that, because...
Today is a special day for the... for me! Yeah!
Today is... do you know what today is? Say it, say it!
Don't be shy, say it!
Yeah! Today is my birthday!
Happy Birthday Zeta~
Selamat Ulang Tahun~
Happy Birthday~
Gitu ga sih lagunya? I don't know.
Is that how the song goes? I don't know.
Oh? What? You're saying something? Huh?
Mmm... Noob? Skill... Skill issue?
You're saying I'm a noob as a secret agent?
Bulls... Okay, I can't say the word. Bulls.
Your lies... You're lying! That can't be true.
I've been working hard. I've got the stamina...
And obviously the intelligence... IQ... IQ二百。
And obviously the intelligence... IQ... IQ 200.
And strength. You know? Like the power as well. Yeah yeah yeah.
So anyways, don't you worry because I've got the perfect thing for today.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah. Have you ever heard of a... ummm...
Of a... of a secret agent school?
Yeah, so... uh, back in my days...
I've been through hell and back, so I invited some transfer students here...
So we can prove that I'm the best secret agent, okay?
So, mmm, we're gonna do some tests together to see...
How tough it is to become a professional secret agent like me.
Like me, like me. Like me! I'm a good example.
Anyways, it reminds me of my... old... 学校... um... you know?
Anyways, it reminds me of my... old... school... um... you know?
But... to be honest... mmm... to be honest... I did feel... mmm...
To be honest, I don't know what we'll be doing yet, but...
Wait. Oh crap. Okay. It's almost time for the first test.
最初のテストが... そろそろ... は... 早く行かないと！
The first test is... almost... I... I gotta go quick!
Bye!
来るなー！
Don't come!
あれ？なんか…
Huh? Something...
なんかさ…
Something like...
なんかみこちのカマキリの威嚇ポーズにビビってる！
It's scared of Mikochi's mantis intimidation pose!
ビビった？ビビった？
Scared? You scared?
あ、ビビってるビビってる！
Ah, it's scared, it's scared!
あれ？
Huh?
これ、みこちゃん分かりました。
Miko-chan has figured this out.
こいつ、雑魚ゾンビです。
This guy is a small-fry zombie.
ざぁ〜こ♡
Sma~ll-fry~ <3
こいつドMかもしれない！
This guy might be a huge masochist!
ドM？！
A masochist?!
みこ向け？みこ向け？
Suitable for Miko? For Miko?
ポンコツ〜♡
Useless~ <3
あ、効いてる効いてる！
Ah, it's working, it's working!
珍しく効いてる。
Unusually, it's working.
ちょっとよわよわゾンビさんなんじゃない？
Isn't this a bit of a weakling zombie?
全然怖くないんですけど〜！
It's not scary at all though~!
余裕かも〜！
Might be easy~!
うぇ〜い！
Ya~y!
みんな〜！
Everyone~!
あ！ゼータ！
Ah! Zeta!
遅れてごめん〜！
Sorry I'm late~!
ヤッホー！
Yahoo!
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
なにこのゾンビ？
What's with this zombie?
あれはよわよわゾンビさんで…
That is a weakling zombie and...
よわよわゾンビがいる〜！
There's a weakling zombie~!
レジェンドスクールの最初のテストにお招きしたけど…
I was invited to the first test of Legend School but...
ゾンビも新入生なのかな？
Is the zombie a new student too?
新入生？！
New student?!
大丈夫なの？
Is it okay?
そうなんだ。でも言葉通じないけどさ、ゾンビに。
Is that so? But language doesn't get through to zombies.
ゼータは言葉、いろんな言葉話せるよね？
Zeta can speak many languages, right?
ゾンビ語も喋れるんじゃないの？
Can't you speak Zombie language too?
そっち？！
That way?!
任せて任せて！
Leave it to me, leave it to me!
おけおけおけ！
Okay okay okay!
う〜あ〜あ〜…
Oo... ah... ah...
ちょっと弱そうかも。
Sounds a bit weak maybe.
え、会話してる？
Eh, are they conversing?
よし！出来た！
Alright! I did it!
出来た？！
You did it?!
おい！ゾンビ！
Oi! Zombie!
何してるの！
What are you doing!
怖がらせろって言ったでしょ！
I told you to be scary!
オリーちゃんだ！
It's Ollie-chan!
I told you to be scary, right?!
What have you been doing?!
怒ってる怒ってる！
She's angry, she's angry!
Apologies.
I probably sent over the weak zombies.
Sorry about that.
Anyways,
I called you guys here for a surprise test
to see if you guys are fit to be a secret agent.
なるほどね。
I see.
なんか分かんないけどウケる。
I don't really get it but it's funny.
なんか分かんないけど受けてみるか。
I don't really get it but let's take the test.
受けてみよう！
Let's take it!
Okay, okay, calm down everyone.
In this test, you will need to guess what is inside the box!
では、この箱の中身を当ててもらうテストになります！
So, this will be a test to guess what is inside this box!
箱の中身〜？！
Inside the box~?!
This requires your investigative skills.
これはあなたたちの推理力が試されます。
This will test your deductive reasoning.
For round 1,
you can feel the object for 30 seconds only.
Have fun.
Can't wait to see your reactions.
いいリアクション期待してるよだって。
She says she expects good reactions.
完全に理解してるから。
I completely understand.
じゃあ、AZKi先輩からかな？
Then, starting with AZKi-senpai?
分かりました。
Understood.
頑張ります。
I'll do my best.
頑張って〜！
Good luck~!
これ、みんなで協力してだよね？
We're doing this together, right?
まぁそうね。情報を集めよう。
Well, yes. Let's gather information.
伝えることに集中したいと思います。
I'll focus on conveying what I feel.
Three, Two, One...
Start!
おお〜！
Ooh~!
え？これ…
Eh? This...
え、コードのような…
Eh, like a cord...
コード？
Cord?
なんだこれ？え、ちょっと待って。
What is this? Eh, wait a minute.
え、なんか、ジタバタしてます。
Eh, something is flailing.
ジタバタ？！
Flailing?!
動いてる！動いてるよ！
It's moving! It's moving!
怖っ！何？
Scary! What?
え、なんか動いているけど…
Eh, it's moving though...
Time's up!
なんか足がバタバタしてるみたいな。
It feels like legs flapping around.
やばい！
Oh no!
変な機械なんじゃないの？
Isn't it some strange machine?
なんか、足がバタバタしてるみたいな感覚…
It feels like legs are flapping around...
え〜！やばい！
Ehh! That's bad!
じゃあ、ミオちゃん！
Then, Mio-chan!
Start!
ほら！
Here goes!
お！お！お！お！
Ooh! Ooh! Ooh! Ooh!
怖い怖い怖い！
Scary scary scary!
は！なんか… は！あ！あ！
Hah! Something... Hah! Ah! Ah!
でも分かったかもこれウチ。
But I might have figured it out.
え？分かった？
Eh? You figured it out?
ああ、なるほど。はいはいはい。
Ah, I see. Yes yes yes.
ああ、元気ですね。
Ah, it's energetic, isn't it.
元気？！
Energetic?!
元気元気。
Energetic energetic.
あ〜、元気だったな〜。すごい元気だった。
Ah, it was energetic. It was very energetic.
元気、元気…
Energetic, energetic...
完全に生きてますやん。
It's completely alive.
Time's up!
あ〜元気だったな〜。すごい元気だった。
Ah, it was energetic. It was very energetic.
絶対生きてるんだ…
It's definitely alive...
ちょっと待って待って。
Wait a minute, wait.
うん、元気だったよね〜。
Yeah, it was energetic~.
えっ？…やだ！
Eh? ...No way!
ガチですか？
Is this for real?
ガチなやつ。
It's the real deal.
ねえ、やめて！
Hey, stop it!
えっ？ゴッドハンド？
Eh? God Hand?
ただ…ブルルルッてなって…
It just went 'brrr' and vibrated...
めっちゃキモっ！
So gross!
ベスティア・ゼータの挑戦
Vestia Zeta's Challenge
行きますよ！
Here I go!
えっ？これ生きてるやん？
Eh? This is alive, isn't it?
えっ？飛んでる？
Eh? Is it flying?
なんか飛びそうだよね。
It looks like it's gonna jump, right?
生きているのか…？
Is it alive...?
なんか…プロペラがついたもの…かも…
Something... with a propeller attached... maybe...
アヒルとかの足が、こうなんか…バタバタバタ…
Like a duck's feet, doing this... flap flap flap...
これはズバリ！カエルのおもちゃです。
This is definitely! A frog toy.
ゼータちゃん…まとめを。
Zeta-chan... give us the summary.
ミオ先輩の答えで！
With Mio-senpai's answer!
カエルのおもちゃ。
A frog toy.
Frog toy
合ってた！すごい！
It was correct! Amazing!
えっ？何がポイントだったんですか？
Eh? What was the clue?
触った感じがピタピタしててて…
It felt sticky when I touched it...
ピョンピョンピョンってしてたから。
Because it was going hop hop hop.
じゃあ、次の問題。
Well then, next question.
大神ミオの挑戦
Ookami Mio's Challenge
えっ？…怖い怖い…
Eh? ...Scary, scary...
本当に怖がっている。
She's really scared.
えっ？…気持ち悪い！
Eh? ...It's gross!
いや…いやー！
No... Nooo!
AZKiの挑戦
AZKi's Challenge
もしゃもしゃしてます。
It feels shaggy.
なんかベタベタしてた。
It felt kinda sticky.
最初驚くんだね、これ。
You get surprised at first, with this.
え？
Eh?
あ…でも、柔らかい。
Ah... but, it's soft.
柔らかい…柔らかい…
Soft... it's soft...
優しい？
Is it kind?
優しい？柔らかい。
Kind? It's soft.
これに関してはちょっとね、ゼータの感覚が狂ってるかもしれない。
Regarding this, Zeta's senses might be a bit off.
何？何？何？
What? What is it?
余計怖いんだけど！
That makes it even scarier!
いいのか？ここで。
Is it okay? To do it here?
いいのか？ここで。ふーん。
Is it okay here? Hmmm.
じゃあ、みこ先輩頑張ってね。
Alright, Miko-senpai, do your best.
ゴッドハンド！
God Hand!
出た！ゴッドハンド！
It appeared! God Hand!
ゴッドリアクション来るぞ！
The God Reaction is coming!
Here comes the God Reaction!
さくらみこの挑戦
Sakura Miko's Challenge
スタート！
Start!
うわぁー！
Uwaaaah!
来た！ゴッドリアクション！
It's here! The God Reaction!
ゴッドリアクション出たよ！
She did the God Reaction!
いや！
No!
手を入れることを躊躇っています。
She is hesitating to put her hand in.
躊躇うよね、これ一回聞いたら。
Of course she'd hesitate after hearing that.
うわぁ、うわぁ！
Uwaa, uwaa!
お前なんか、引くじゃないか！
Hey, you're pulling away aren't you!
引くじゃないか！ちょっとこれ…
It's pulling back! Wait, this...
ちょっとするよな…
It does do that a bit...
食べ物？
Is it food?
いや、そんなことはない。
No, I don't think so.
魚？
A fish?
なんか出てる！触れてる！
Something's sticking out! It's touching!
ちょっとヤバイことが起きてるじゃないか！
Something dangerous is happening!
え？ヤバイこと？
Eh? Dangerous?
あの箱の中で、事件が起きている！
There's an incident happening inside that box!
マスクをしてたと思うんだよ。
I think it was wearing a mask.
だからうちは、ピエロなんじゃないかと思います。
So, I think it's a clown.
えーっと、白い…白塗りの女性の顔。
Umm, a white... white-painted woman's face.
怖えーよ！
That's scary!
マスク？その答え怖えーよ！
A mask? That answer is scary!
おそらく…YAGOOのカツラ。
Probably... YAGOO's wig.
えぇーー！？
Eeeeh!?
絶対カツラだったと思うんだよ。
I'm absolutely sure it was a wig.
ロングヘアーYAGOO？
Long hair YAGOO?
いや、ロングヘアーYAGOOの可能性、ある。
No, there's a possibility it's Long Hair YAGOO.
名探偵みこ先輩を信じようかな。
I think I'll trust the Great Detective Miko-senpai.
お！
Oh!
答えはー…
The answer is...
ロングヘアーYAGOO！
Long Hair YAGOO!
あちゃー、残念だね。
Uh-oh, too bad.
不正解です！
Wrong answer!
なんか怖いんだけど…
It's kinda scary though...
いやぁー！
Kyaaaah!
当たってた！
She was right!
ミオちゃん当たってたよ！
Mio-chan was right!
当たってるよ！
She got it right!
当たってるの怖い！
Getting it right is scary!
次の問題、お願いします！
Next question, please!
お願いします！
Please!
じゃあ、ゴッドハンドみこ先輩から行ってみましょうか。
Then, let's start with God Hand Miko-senpai again.
名探偵、ここで決めてね。
Detective, settle it here.
名探偵、頼むよ。
Detective, we're counting on you.
さくらみこの挑戦
Sakura Miko's Challenge
ゴーゴーゴー！
Go go go!
うわぁー！
Uwaaaah!
待って、待って！
Wait, wait!
待って、濡れてる！
Wait, it's wet!
ちょっと今日一の絶叫出たけど大丈夫？
That was the loudest scream today, are you okay?
うぇ！
Ueh!
え？え？え？
Eh? Eh? Eh?
なんかチクチクしてて…
It feels kind of prickly...
チクチク？
Prickly?
痛いってこと？
Does it hurt?
ヌルヌルっていうか、濡れてて…
It's slimy... or rather, it's wet...
濡れてる！？
Wet!?
全部にトゲトゲがあります！
There are spikes all over it!
全部にトゲトゲある？
Spikes all over?
で、いっぱいいる！
And there's a lot of them!
生き物！？
Living things!?
トゲトゲした生き物！
Spiky living things!
待って、いっぱいいるってなに！？
Wait, what do you mean 'a lot'!?
うわぁぁぁ！
Uwaaaah!
どうする？
What do we do?
あずき先輩の方がいいかな？
Maybe AZKi-senpai should go?
せーの、ハンド！
Ready, hand!
交換できるのかな？
Can we switch?
AZKiの挑戦
AZKi's Challenge
あずき先輩！ゴー！
AZKi-senpai! Go!
はい！
Okay!
へ？なに？
Eh? What?
お？
Oh?
なんか濡れてる？
Is it wet?
濡れてる。
It's wet.
やっぱ濡れてるんだ。
So it IS wet.
なんか湿っています。
It's somewhat damp.
湿ってる？
Damp?
すごい高めなんだ、これ。
It's piled pretty high.
え、なにこの…
Eh, what is this...
トゲトゲした球体のような…
Spiky sphere-like things...
球体？
Spheres?
球体と、その下にもトゲトゲしたものが…
Spheres, and below them more spiky things...
トゲトゲがいっぱいあるぞ？
There's a lot of spikes?
痛くはない？
It doesn't hurt?
痛くはないけど…
It doesn't hurt but...
え、これなんだ？
Eh, what is this?
なんだこれ？
What is it?
全然わからない！
I don't know at all!
え、それやばいやつじゃん！
Eh, that's bad then!
なんだこれ！？
What IS this!?
なんか湿ってる…
It's kind of damp...
次ミオちゃんですかね？
Next is Mio-chan, I guess?
えー？最後ゼータに決めてもらおうよ！
Eeh? Let's have Zeta decide at the end!
そうしよう、そうしよう。
Let's do that.
なんかやだな、その感想聞いた状態でやるの、触るのちょっとやだかも。
I don't like touching it after hearing those impressions.
大神ミオの挑戦
Ookami Mio's Challenge
ゴー！
Go!
やだな、濡れてるっていう前情報で嫌だ。
I hate the prior info that it's wet.
濡れてるよ。
It IS wet.
あー！やっぱ濡れてるな！
Aah! It really is wet!
濡れてる？
Wet?
濡れてる。
It's wet.
あー、おっと、濡れてる！
Ah, oh, it's wet!
濡れてるけど…
It's wet but...
なんか硬くて…
It's sort of hard...
下にたくさんいる！
There are many of them below!
いっぱいいるんだよ！
There's a lot, right!
たくさんいるぞ！
There are many!
なんだ、これ？
What is this?
え、これでさ、あんまり見かけないやつの気がする。
Eh, I feel like I don't see this kind of thing often.
見かけない？
You don't see it?
Uncommon?
むずいんだ！
It's difficult!
出た！
I did it!
行こう！
Let's go!
頑張るゼータ！
I'll do my best zeta!
それでは…
Well then...
ベスティア・ゼータの挑戦
Vestia Zeta's Challenge
スタート！
Start!
うわ！おお！
Whoa! Oh!
うわ！あー！
Whoa! Ah!
あ、OK、OK。OK。
Ah, OK, OK. OK.
早い！わかったかも。
Fast! I might know what it is.
我々はあんまり馴染みないけど…
We aren't very familiar with it, but...
ゼータは馴染みあるの？
Is Zeta familiar with it?
馴染みがある、もしかしたら。
I might be familiar with it, possibly.
これいっぱい触ったことあるかも。
I might have touched this a lot.
馴染み深い？
Very familiar?
馴染み深いんだよ、きっと。
It's surely familiar.
ゼータにとっては。
For Zeta, at least.
我々にしたらちょっと難しいかも。
For us, it might be a bit difficult.
Time's up!
イエーイ！OK！
Yay! OK!
これはね…うんうんうん。
This is... yeah yeah yeah.
おそらくこれは…
Probably this is...
ウニの仲間。
A friend of sea urchins.
ウニ！？
Sea urchin?!
あずきの答えは…
AZKi's answer is...
苔。
Moss.
なんかちょっとずついっぱい生えている感じ。
It feels like a lot of little things growing.
でも確かに湿ってたしね。
But it was certainly damp.
うちの答えは…
My answer is...
ライチ。
Lychee.
ゼータはね、多分…
Zeta thinks, probably...
インドネシア果物と近いかも。
It might be close to an Indonesian fruit.
いっぱいトゲトゲを…
Lots of spikes...
なんていう食べ物？
What's the food called?
名前はランブータン。
The name is Rambutan.
ランブータン？
Rambutan?
でもわかんない、ここにはランブータンいないのかな。
But I don't know if Rambutan exists here.
自信持っていこう。
Let's be confident.
ゼータが一番わかってたよ。
Zeta understood it the best.
一番自信あったじゃん。
She had the most confidence.
じゃあそれでいきましょうよ。
Then let's go with that.
答えは、せーの…
The answer is, one two...
ランブータン！
Rambutan!
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding!
Correct answer!
やったー！すごい！
Yay! Amazing!
ちょっと待って、うちライチとか言ったけど…
Wait a minute, I said Lychee but...
全然違うわ。
It's totally different.
何これ！？
What is this?!
ライチの味がするかも。
It might taste like Lychee.
味は似てる。
The taste is similar.
初めて見た。
I've never seen it before.
甘いの？
Is it sweet?
ちょっと甘っぽい。
It's a little sweet-ish.
There seems to have been correct and incorrect answers.
But...
Zeta!
It seems like your investigative skills are not quite up to par yet.
You need to work harder.
Or, in other words...
SKILL ISSUE!
Skill issue ってどういうこと！？
What do you mean 'skill issue'?!
見て、スキルが問題のゼータだよ！
Look, it's Zeta with the skill issue!
She's getting mad!
あっ、怒っちゃった！
Ah, she got mad!
Oh dear!
Wow, you can't even solve that!
まったく、こんなのも解けないなんて！
Geez, to think you can't even solve this!
Everyone else, you did great!
みんな、よくやったわ！
Everyone, you did well!
Good luck on the next test!
See y'all!
またね！
See ya!
え、ゼータも頑張ったのにな。
Eh, but Zeta did her best too.
さっき笑ったの？
Did you just laugh?
ちょっとナメてたね。
It was underestimating us.
笑ってんじゃねえよ！
Don't you be laughing!
笑ってんじゃねえお前！
Don't you laugh, you!
弱い者いじめすんな！
Don't bully the weak!
かわいそう！
Poor thing!
あずき様！？
AZKi-sama?!
優しそう！
She looks kind!
もっと、床に這いつくばりなさい。
Crawl on the floor more.
あずき様ー！
AZKi-sama!
ありがとね、みんな来てくれて。
Thanks everyone for coming.
誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
次のテストの時間だから、行ってくるね！
It's time for the next test, so I'm going!
頑張れー！
Good luck!
バイバーイ！
Bye bye!
ゾンビ、もっと祝いなさいよ。
Zombie, celebrate more.
ゼータを祝って！
Celebrate Zeta!
Wait, there's like a ring.
Wait, is this like a boxing ring?
Wait, what am I gonna have to do here?
No way. Are we gonna have to fight?
I'm not good at fighting though.
I mean I can try, but...
Happy birthday, Zeta!
Long time no see.
This is Amelia Watson.
hololive EN's number one time-traveling detective!
How've you been?
I've been good!
How are you?
Ah, glad to see you're doing well!
Yeah. I prepared the second test.
But we also have other transfer students.
Let's call them in now!
Don't let the first contestant's size fool you!
People tremble when they hear her name and her infamous line!
"Small but mighty, always rock hard."
"I'm rocking in!"
Please welcome... Koseki Bijou!
Koseki Bijou!
Happy birthday Zeta!
Today I'm rock hard just for you.
KOSEKI BIJOU
Coming to the ring, she's the hero we didn't ask for,
but somehow still believe in!
She's everyone's last hope.
Because all the good ones were busy!
Her line is:
"Meet your end, and... despair!"
"Haiyah!"
Happy birthday Zeta!
I'm taking you down!
Down... under.
IRyS
Ladies and gentlemen!
Hide your dumbbells and protect your ego!
Because this grim reaper doesn't just reap souls,
she rips the gym apart!
Her favorite line is:
"Only time can out-bench me."
Please welcome... Mori Calliope!
Mori Calliope!
Happy birthday Zeta!
MORI CALLIOPE
Yeah boi!
Good! Everyone has gathered, right?
This is probably a big surprise, huh?
And I'm sure you're all wondering what kind of test this is gonna be!
Anyone have any guesses?
Don't say ground pounding.
She just said that!
Oh, correct!
We're holding a physical test using this long stick...
...with these Bazo weights to determine if you are fit enough...
...to pass off as a secret agent!
RIP Bozo.
Okay, okay.
For level 1 of the physical test!
First, lift Bazo from the ring mat up to your hips...
...as many times as you can within 30 seconds.
For level 2,
the mat will be bumpy.
You'll do the same thing as many times as you can...
...within 30 seconds.
And for the last level,
you'll stand on the bumpy mat and balance a cup on your head!
Make sure you don't drop it, and lift Bazo up!
Well then, are you guys ready?
Let's go!
Okay, who's ready for the physical test?
Maybe we should have... Bijou start first?
I got it!
Okay, are you ready?
Yeah!
Start!
One! Two!
Three! Four!
Five! Six!
Seven! Eight!
Nine!
Keep it up! Ten!
Eleven! Double digits!
Twelve! Thirteen!
Fourteen!
Fifteen! Sixteen!
Seventeen! Eighteen!
Nineteen! Twenty!
Twenty-one!
Time's up!
Now IRyS!
IRyS!
I got this.
Yes, full potential!
Start!
One! Two!
Prove them wrong! Three!
Four! Five!
Six! Seven!
Eight! Nine!
Ten!
Eleven! Twelve!
Thirteen! Fourteen!
Fifteen! Sixteen!
Seventeen! Eighteen!
Nineteen! Twenty!
Twenty-one!
Time's up!
It's a tie!
Start!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Six!
Seven!
Eight!
Nine!
Ten!
Eleven!
Twelve!
Thirteen!
Fourteen!
Fifteen!
Sixteen!
Seventeen!
Eighteen!
Nineteen!
Twenty!
Twenty-one!
Twenty-two!
Twenty-three!
Twenty-four!
Twenty-five!
Twenty-six!
Twenty-seven!
Twenty-eight!
Twenty-nine!
Time's up!
大丈夫、大丈夫。
It's okay, it's okay.
Anyway, that was weak.
Twenty-nine!
Like I said...
You have to show us what you're made of.
Okay...
You got this!
Okay, okay, okay.
You gonna count down for me?
Of course!
Ready?
Start!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Six!
Seven!
Eight!
Nine!
Ten!
Eleven!
Twelve!
Thirteen!
Fourteen!
Fifteen!
Sixteen!
Seventeen!
Eighteen!
Nineteen!
Twenty!
Twenty-one!
Twenty-two!
Twenty-three!
Twenty-four!
Twenty-five!
Twenty-six!
Twenty-seven!
Twenty-eight!
Twenty-nine!
Thirty!
Time's up!
Woah!
I can't stand up!
You did great!
That was crazy.
She is a secret agent after all.
Okay, now who's ready for Level 2?
I don't know about this one...
Wait a minute, that's not fair!
Those are Biboo's brothers and sisters!
That's not fair!
She has an advantage!
Pebbles! You see this?
They're loving it!
Oh, it hurts though...
Ready?
Start!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Six!
Seven!
Eight!
Nine!
Ten!
Eleven!
Twelve!
Thirteen!
Fourteen!
Fifteen!
Sixteen!
Seventeen!
Eighteen!
Nineteen!
Twenty!
Twenty-one!
Twenty-two!
Twenty-three!
Twenty-four!
Twenty-five!
Twenty-six!
Twenty-seven!
Twenty-eight!
Twenty-nine!
Thirty!
Time's up!
Thirty-four!
Was that her full power?
That's Level 2!
Give me strength!
No, don't step on them!
Show them who you are!
Take your time...
How does it feel?
Ready!
Start!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Six!
Seven!
Eight!
Nine!
Ten!
Eleven!
Twelve!
Thirteen!
Fourteen!
Fifteen!
Sixteen!
Seventeen!
Eighteen!
Nineteen!
Twenty!
Twenty-one!
Time's up!
She's lost for words.
Are you okay?
It's not like the pebbles are gonna help me.
So...
I'll try to just do my best.
You got this!
Start!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Six!
Seven!
Eight!
Nine!
Ten!
Eleven!
Twelve!
Thirteen!
Fourteen!
Fifteen!
Sixteen!
Seventeen!
Eighteen!
Nineteen!
Twenty!
Twenty-one!
Twenty-two!
Twenty-three!
Twenty-four!
Twenty-five!
Twenty-six!
Twenty-seven!
Twenty-eight!
Twenty-nine!
Thirty!
Time's up!
Thirty-three!
Your form was perfect.
32!
Yeah!
I'll take it.
Step on those pebbles, like they were...
Biboo gives you permission.
Yeah, Biboo gives me permission.
Whaaa!
She's going Super Saiyan.
Yeah!
Something's coming out of me!
All right, is that all? Are you ready?
Yeah!
3, 2, 1, Go!
Start!
One! Two!
Three! Four! Five! Six! Seven!
Eight! Nine! Ten! Eleven!
Mama! Mama!
13! 14! 15!
16! 17! 18! 19! 20!
21! 22! 23! 24!
25! 26! 27! 28! 29!
30! 31! 32!
Oh my god! 33!
34! 35! 36! 37!
Time's up!
Yaaay!
My butt...
Ow! It hurts so bad.
It is over!
I'm glad you guys are having fun!
Level 3 of the physical test is gonna be pretty tough, though.
You guys ready?
For Level 3, I've got a little something...
behind me, which is a...
A cup!
Would you like a cup of tea?
Um, maybe later.
It's tea time!
Uh, while you guys are stepping... uh, while we are stepping on the...
...bumpy mat...
We're also gonna be balancing this cup on top of our head like this.
Oh, it's so over.
You'll have to use the mat?
Yeah, we still have...
It's a combination of everything!
Yeah.
And while lifting as well, of course.
Yeah, it doesn't affect us at all.
At all! It doesn't affect us at all!
Okay. Crown me.
Crown... Crown the princess.
Oh, oh...
There you go. It's so over.
It's so over.
Pray to the people. Are you ready?
It's not over! Hold on!
Remember to use your butt and your legs.
Okay, butt and my legs. Okay form.
Okay. Ready?
Are you ready? Yeah!
Okay. Start!
One! Two! Three!
Four! Five! Six! Seven!
Eight! Nine!
Oh no!
Ten! Eleven! Twelve! 13!
14! 15! 16! 17!
18! 19! 20! 21!
22! 23! 24! 25!
26! 27! 28! 29!
30! 31! 32!
Time's up!
Yaaaay!
I like how the cup was like, stuck on her head.
Yeah, that was funny.
It turned over and it was hot on her head.
28!
IRyS. Hybrid.
Princess.
I have...
Beautiful posture.
Exactly.
You have the posture.
This is my strong point.
Because I'm really good at keeping it on my head.
Wait a sec. Don't put it on me yet.
Okay, you may place it on my head. The crown.
Milady. Here goes the cup.
Thank you. Oh, it's beautiful.
My coronation.
3, 2, 1, Start!
One! Two! Three!
Four! Five! Six! Seven!
Eight! Nine! Ten!
Eleven! Twelve!
Noooo! Noooo!
Go for it!
Nine! Ten! Eleven!
Twelve! Oh my god! No no no!
Time's up!
I'm proud of you.
This stupid cup!
Stupid, stupid cup!
Don't blame the cup!
Maybe my good form will come in handy here.
Yeah, exactly.
You may place the tiara on my head.
No, you have to step on it first.
Oh, come on.
It's the pain before the gain.
Pain before the game?
Pain is beauty.
I shall place it on top of your crown...
...so you have double crown.
Awesome.
Okay.
Are you ready, coach?
Maybe.
3, 2, 1, Start!
One! Two! Three!
Four! Five! Six! Seven!
Eighteen!
Nineteen!
Twenty!
Twenty-one!
Twenty-two!
Twenty-three!
Twenty-four!
Twenty-five!
Twenty-six!
Oh, my posture!
Time's up!
That was my goal!
Got the 24!
And I didn't lose the cup even once!
You sure this cup is not rigged?
Super glue?
Was it super glue?
Let's really test it, get in there...
Zeta's turn!
Directly right in the center of your head.
This is like the best birthday ever.
Yay, I'm glad!
Now then, are you ready?
Three, two, one, Start!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Six!
Seven!
Eight!
Nine!
Ten!
Eleven!
Twelve!
Thirteen!
Fourteen!
Fifteen!
Sixteen!
Seventeen!
Eighteen!
Nineteen!
Twenty!
Twenty-one!
Twenty-two!
Twenty-three!
Twenty-four!
Twenty-five!
Twenty-six!
Time's up!
Yay!
Twenty-six!
You did it!
Twenty-six is the final number!
Does that mean the scores are what I think it is?
I think so!
Is anyone keeping score?
Staff-san has been keeping score for us!
You are a winner!
I am a winner?
What matters is what's inside.
Seems like you guys completed the test! Woohoo!
Some of you were able to lift pretty well.
Maybe not for some, though.
It was so much fun just watching!
But come on, Zeta!
You're the birthday girl!
You should be showing us your crazy skills or something!
Prove it to us next test, okay?
Well then, thank you for having me!
This is Amelia Watson signing off.
Until next time!
Bye!
Thank you so much!
Good luck!
See ya!
あいつを狙おう！
Let's target her!
やめてくれ！やめてくれ！
Stop it! Stop it!
楽しそう！楽しそう！
Looks fun! Looks fun!
ゼータ？
Zeta?
何水鉄砲持ってるの？
Why are you holding a water gun?
やめて！やめて！
Stop! Stop!
撃てるよ！
I can shoot!
どういうこと？
What does this mean?
誰か説明して〜！
Someone explain~!
Bokobokobo~ Kobo Kanaeru at your service!
Let me be your sun to shine your day! Ehehe!
ゼータ、誕生日おめでとう！
Zeta, happy birthday!
I already told them what to do before you came here,
so they know the rules!
この水鉄砲で君のエイム力を確かめるよ！
We're gonna be testing your aim skills with this water gun!
In shooting level 1, we will see how many immobile targets you can hit within 30 seconds.
In level 2, we will see how many moving targets you can hit within 30 seconds.
And level 3 will test if you can hit the targets on the moving zombie.
誰が最強のエイム力を持っているかな？
Who do you think is the best shooter here?
オレア！オレア！
Orea! Orea!
トワ達みんななんとFPSやってるんでね！
We all play FPS games, you know!
そうだね！
That's right!
私はやってないけどね。
I don't play them though.
どういうこと？誰か説明して〜
What do you mean? Someone explain~
私も負けないよー！
I won't lose either!
Level 1
こちらに！
Over here!
動かない的があるので...
There are stationary targets...
こちらをみんなで一人ずつ撃っていこうかなと思います。
...so let's all shoot them one by one.
頑張るー！
I'll do my best!
順番どうしましょう？
How should we decide the order?
一番！
First!
やりたい！やりたい！
I wanna do it! I wanna do it!
Me too! Me too!
やったー！
Yay!
まつりちゃんは見やすい位置...
I'll go to a spot where it's easy to see...
しょうがないね。
Can't be helped.
撃たない三人はね、ここら辺で見て待ってましょう。
The three not shooting can watch from here.
はーい。
Okay.
3...
2...
1...
スタート！
Start!
はい！
Yes!
おお、うま！
Oh, so good!
ごめん！
Sorry!
え？
Eh?
マシーンなの？
Is she a machine?
まさかパーフェクトおじさんじゃない？
Isn't that 'Mr. Perfect'?
ごめん！ごめん！
Sorry! Sorry!
パーフェクトおじさんじゃない？
Isn't she 'Mr. Perfect'?
ごめん！
Sorry!
え、うますぎる！
Whoa, too good!
ヤバい！
Dangerous!
すごすぎる！
Too amazing!
残り15秒！
15 seconds left!
え？！
Eh?!
これみんなには分かんないけど、ぶっちゃけ難しいからねこれ。
You guys might not realize, but this is honestly super hard.
すごいすごいすごい！
Amazing, amazing!
偏差とかもなしに...
Without even needing to lead the shots...
え、これ最後？
Eh, is this the last one?
最後？！
Last one?!
えー？！
Ehh?!
あと一個！あと一個！
One more! One more!
はい！
Hup!
おおー！！
Oooooh!!
終わっちゃったー！
Finished!
怖っ！
Scary!
無限に...
Infinitely...
まつりちゃんは...
Matsuri-chan...
一発も外さず全て取れましたー！
...got them all without missing a single shot!
やったー！すごーい！
Yay! Amazing!
え、すごすぎる...
Eh, that's too good...
うますぎるよね。
Way too good, right?
なんかちょっと行きづらいわ。
Kinda hard to follow that.
ハードル下げていこう。
Let's lower the hurdle.
あ、マジ？
Ah, really?
じゃあトワ様でしょ、次は。
Then it's Towa-sama next, right?
あ、トワ様だ！
Ah, Towa-sama it is!
じゃあトワ...
Okay then, Towa...
頑張れ！
Do your best!
いけるいける！
You can do it!
支えるよ、支える感じでいくよ。
I'll support you, I'll go with a supporting vibe.
じゃあカウントお願いします。
Start the count, please.
大事、大事。
Important, important.
3...
2...
1...
スタート！
Start!
ここ！
Here!
はい！
Hup!
ここ！
Here!
おお！
Oh!
おい！
Oi!
速い速い！
Fast, fast!
はい！
Yes!
あー！
Ah!
ここ！
Here!
順調順調！
Smooth sailing!
はい、ここ！
Okay, here!
うまい！
Good!
え、ちょっと待って！
Eh, wait a sec!
はい！
Yup!
うまい、うまい！
Good, good!
めっちゃ速い！
So fast!
ここ！
Here!
はい！
Hup!
え、うま！
Eh, good!
ここ！
Here!
よし！
Alright!
いい感じ！
Nice feeling!
やったー！
I did it!
すごーい！
Amazing!
だんだん超えてくんだ、これ。
It's gradually getting harder to beat.
次どうする？
Who's next?
いやー...
No way...
先にやった方がいい！
Better to go first!
じゃあ、じゃあ、じゃあ...
Okay, okay, okay...
トリはね...
The grand finale is...
とりあえずね。
For now.
作戦あるんだ。
I have a strategy.
下半身作戦！
Lower Body Strategy!
下半身作戦？
Lower Body Strategy?
下半身を安定させブレないようにする。
Stabilize the lower body to prevent shaking.
安定、安定。
Stable, stable.
ポーズだっせぇ！
That pose is so lame!
ダサすぎる！
Too lame!
これでいくから。
I'm going with this.
3...
2...
1...
どうぞ！
Go ahead!
オラ！
Ora!
頑張れー！
Do your best!
頑張れ！
Fight!
頑張れー！
Go for it!
安定させて...
Stabilize...
当たってる、当たってる！
Hit, hit!
適当に撃つ...
Just shooting randomly...
あ、でも惜しい惜しい。
Ah, but close, close.
ヤバい！
Oh no!
空に...
Into the sky...
もっと上！
Higher!
頑張って、頑張って！
Come on, come on!
いいよ、それ空だぞ！
Nice, but that's the sky!
ラプラスの結果は、まあ...
La+'s result is, well...
ボイドということで。
...void.
イェーイ！
Yay!
最後、行きますか！
Shall we go for the last one?
行きます！
I'm going!
頑張れ！
Good luck!
ということで、じゃあ最後ゼータ。
Alright, so lastly, Zeta.
一秒で？
In one second?
いやいやいや。
No no no.
準備オッケー？
Ready OK?
準備オッケー。
Ready OK.
いくよ！
Here we go!
3...
2...
1...
ゴー！
Go!
お、いいよ！
Oh, nice!
いいよ！
Nice!
すごいすごい！
Amazing!
思ったよりうまい！
Better than I thought!
うまいよ！
You're good!
いや、これは...
No, this is...
全然余裕、余裕！
Totally easy, easy!
まだ、まだ！
Still, still!
どこだ？
Where?
どこどこ？
Where, where?
右右右！
Right right right!
そっちそっち！
That way!
下です、下です！
Below, below!
どこにある？
Where is it?
どこだ？
Where?
あれ？
Huh?
どこだ？
Where is it?
なくなった？
Did it disappear?
バグか、これは？
Is this a bug?
神様が手伝ってもらったか？
Did God help us out?
どこだ？
Where was it?
あれ？
Huh?
なんかギリギリ滑り込みで...
Somehow slid in just in time...
判定だー！
It counted!
イェーイ！
Yay!
Level 2
あちらをご覧ください！
Please look over there!
はい！
Yes!
動いてる！
They're moving!
無茶苦茶！
That's messy!
はい、頑張っていきましょう。
Okay, let's do our best.
じゃあ誰から行く？
So, who's going first?
おるぞ、おるぞ！
I'm here, I'm here!
私も行きたい！
I want to go too!
譲る譲る譲る！
I'll yield, I'll yield!
もう言っちゃったから、じゃあラプラス。
Since you said it, La+ goes.
もう言っちゃったからね。
Since I already said it.
いいんだ。
That's fine.
やったもん勝ちでヤバい。
First come first served is crazy.
ではいきましょう、ラプラス。
Then let's go, La+.
3...
2...
1...
スタート！
Start!
このゲームには必勝法がある！
There is a winning strategy for this game!
めっちゃ回っとるやん！
She's spinning like crazy!
目が回る！
I'm getting dizzy!
当たらん！
Not hitting!
ずるい！
Unfair!
後ろから撃ってるのヤバいって！
Shooting from behind is crazy!
当たってないよ！
You're not hitting!
前見て！
Look forward!
裏だ！裏だ！
It's the back! It's the back!
あと5秒しかないよ！
Only 5 seconds left!
一個しか倒してないよ！
You only got one!
頑張れ！
Do your best!
Time's up!
一個... すごいよ一個。
One... one is amazing.
ゼータ行きたい？
Zeta, wanna go?
ゼータ行きたい！
Zeta wants to go!
はい！じゃあゼータ行きます！
Okay! Zeta is going!
行きます！
I'm going!
ラプラスみたいに後ろ向かなくていい？
You don't need to turn your back like Laplus?
あ、大丈夫。
Ah, I'm fine.
メンタル調整行きましょう！
Let's go for a mental reset!
Start!
頑張れ！
Go go!
あー、裏面だったな。
Ah, it was the back side.
これもう後ろだから！
This is already the back!
Time's up!
残念、ゼータ達裏面です。
Too bad, Zeta and co. got the back side.
めちゃくちゃ難しい...
It's so difficult...
これムズいよ！
This is hard!
最後やだから祭行かせてください。
Since it's the last one, let Matsuri go.
もう行っちゃった。
She's already going.
祭り先輩、行くぞ！
Matsuri-senpai, let's go!
Start!
お、上手い！
Oh, nice!
ムズいんだからこれ！
Because this is actually hard!
Time's up!
二個か...
Two, huh...
一点集中！
Focus on one point!
アドバイスを生かし、やろうかな。
I guess I'll use that advice.
トワちんの挑戦！
Towachin's challenge!
Start!
ヤバい、こっち向け！
Crap, face this way!
あ、裏だ！
Ah, it's the back!
タイミングだ、タイミングだ。
It's timing, it's timing.
Time's up!
これ難しいんだよ！
This is really hard!
一枚でした！
It was one!
Level 3
ゾンビ！
Zombie!
気持ち悪い！
Gross!
動く的になってます！
It's a moving target!
トワちんから、じゃあ行きましょう。
Starting with Towachin, let's go.
Start!
速っ！
So fast!
おい、こっち向け！
Hey, face this way!
回るんだ！
It spins!
よっしゃー！
Alright!
ギリギリです！
That was close!
二つ、なんと割れました！
Somehow, two were broken!
じゃあ姉さんね。
Okay, big sister's turn.
頑張るぞ！
I'll do my best!
Start!
速っ！
Fast!
So fast!
3秒で終わりました。
Finished in 3 seconds.
まずいよこれ
This is bad.
やっちゃったやっちゃった
She totally did it.
今まつりちゃんが３秒で撃ち抜いちゃったということは
Since Matsuri-chan just shot it down in 3 seconds...
多分もう次ゾンビは「あ、この動きしちゃいけないな」って風になって
The next zombie will probably learn not to move like that.
やばい学習するタイプだ
Oh no, it's the learning type!
学習ゾンビなんだ
It's a learning zombie.
ちょっと待ってじゃあ先にやる！
Wait, then I'll go first!
先にやる！
I'll do it first!
主役が最後だよな
The main character goes last, right?
Start!
当たるんかい！
It hits?!
なんで当たるんだよ！
Why did it hit?!
やばい！
Crap!
頭抜けるよ！
The head comes off!
撃て撃て撃て撃て！
Shoot, shoot, shoot!
撃ちなさい！
Shoot it!
やばい、ちょっと途中我慢できなかった
Crap, I couldn't hold back in the middle.
ムカつきすぎて
It was too annoying.
最後、最後の挑戦はゼータ！
Lastly, the final challenge is Zeta!
Go!
うわ！めっちゃ動いてる！
Whoa! It's moving so much!
回ってる！
It's spinning!
頭だけだ！
Only the head!
Clear
Guys! みんなー！
Guys! Everyone!
Should we see who got the most points in this fest?
え、まつりが１２点
Eh, Matsuri is 12 points.
で、トワちんが１１点
And Towachin is 11 points.
で、ゼータが１０点
And Zeta is 10 points.
そしてラプラスが...
And La+ is...
４点！？
4 points?!
４点...
4 points...
ラプラスが最下位！
La+ is last place!
１位を選べよ！
Pick the 1st place one!
Wooow! Congrats! すーごーい！
Wooow! Congrats! Aweeesome!
おめでとー！
Congrats!
You guys did very well!
みんなほんとによく頑張ったね！
You all really did your best!
And best of all, I'm glad everyone had fun.
でも何より、みんなが楽しんでくれて嬉しかった。
But most of all, I'm happy you all had fun.
I can't wait to see how much more you can improve...
Oi.
Um... I'm... I'm talking here.
ちょっと... こっちが喋ってるんだけど？
Hey... I'm talking over here?
Oi! Listen to Kobo!
Anyway, Zeta!
ま、とにかくゼータ！
Well, anyway Zeta!
You still have a long, long way to go to become a full-fledged secret agent, okay?
まだまだ遠い道のりだよ？いい？
Still a long road? Okay?
Yeah, let's have a match one day!
うん、勝負しよう！
Yeah, let's have a match!
Bye! See ya~
バーイ！またね〜
Byee! See ya later~
That was such a crazy game...
I got wet...
濡れちゃったよ
I got all wet.
But, I heard there's gonna be announcements today...
so are you guys ready for the announcements?
では、告知です！お願いします！
Well then, the announcement! Please!
ジャジャーン！
Ta-da!
うわー眩しい！
Wow, so bright!
She's shining so bright...
Angel costume...
清楚ゼータ来た！
Seiso Zeta is here!
どう？可愛いでしょ？
How is it? Cute, right?
Aku mau! Siapa yang mau? Aku aku!
I want it! Who wants it? Me, me!
じゃ、こちらをご覧ください。どうぞ！
Well then, please take a look at this. Go ahead!
ジャジャーン！
Ta-da!
So, have acrylic diorama...
which you can put on your table later, we will explain.
And then we have a cap, no cap, okay.
We have a plushie, look at me!
And not only that, there will of course be voice...
uh sorry why did I say that voice...
There will be voice pack, and also bonus card as well.
Who wants bonus cards? Me!
So, I bet you guys are interested in this, yeah definitely.
Kalau kalian tertarik bakal ada enam item ya guys.
If you are interested, there will be six items, guys.
Acrylic diorama, haori...
kucing... eh kucing... ada topi, ada juga boneka...
cat... er cat... there is a cap, there is also a plushie...
いっぱいありますよね。
There's a lot, right?
Bonus card, there is also bonus cards, so...
Yeah!
Definitely, um, we're gonna get into it but...
stay, stay there. We're not, we're not done yet.
はい、次、どうぞ！
Yes, next, please!
Jajaan!
Ta-da!
This is my acrylic diorama. So cute.
あるてらママ先生、Thank you so much sensei.
Arutera-mama sensei, thank you so much sensei.
ママありがとう！
Thanks Mama!
Mama's drawing is always so cute.
可愛いでしょうね。可愛い。
It's cute, right? Cute.
ゼータ飛んでるよ。凄くない？
Zeta is flying. Isn't that amazing?
It's super duper cute!
I'm having a... well I almost said allergic reaction.
I am having a... do you know that cuteness aggression?
Yeah. That's what I'm feeling. It's so cute!
Okay!
Of course, we're gonna go to the next one.
There's so much more.
じゃ、次、どうぞ！
Then, next, please!
Jajaan!
Ta-da!
何だと！？羽織！？
What is this!? Haori!?
The Vestia Zeta Haori.
I know that you guys would love to wear this at like events...
or like concerts, or maybe you know for future fests.
Next fes, I mean... you guys can wear it together.
You can like huddle up, wear the same haori.
It would be so cute, right?
I mean I'm wearing a uniform so... this can be your uniform.
ライブの時とか。
Like during live concerts.
可愛いでしょう。
It's cute, right?
Like if everyone like use it together it's gonna be so cute.
Lucu banget guys, haori.
It's really cute guys, haori.
Aku nggak tahu mau ngomong apa, pokoknya ini keren banget.
I don't know what to say, anyway this is really cool.
Karena desainnya tuh pertama simpel.
Because the design is firstly simple.
Terus belakangnya tuh kelihatan Zeta.
Then on the back you can see Zeta.
Terus nggak norak gitu lho guys.
Then it's not tacky, you know guys.
Kayak keren aja. Kayak simpel, keren, cool.
It's just cool. Like simple, cool, cool.
Jadi kalian juga pakenya bisa ke mana aja, nggak harus kayak konser-konser doang.
So you guys can wear it anywhere, not just for like concerts.
You can like wear this like outside of concerts as well...
cause like it's like a sophisticated...
Elegant... I wouldn't say elegant. It's like a cool looking...
like toned down haori you know.
So befitting for me, the coolest secret agent.
Okay anyways, there's more. There's more.
次の... どうぞ！
Next one... please!
Jajaan! Wow.
Ta-da! Wow.
Uwe.
Uweee Cap.
I almost choked on myself.
It's so good. It's a baseball cap.
It's so cool. You can use this to shield yourself from the sun.
Like I do because I hate the sun.
There's like uwe written on top of the cap.
可愛い、uwe書いてるよ。
Cute, uwe is written on it.
そうそうそうそう。ゼータのセリフuwe... って書いてる。
Yes yes yes yes. Zeta's line uwe... is written.
可愛いでしょう。
Cute, right?
Of course there's like my neko... ah not neko... my hair buns...
Of course there's like my cat... ah not cat... my hair buns...
Kuping... kuping Zeta.
Ears... Zeta's ears.
There's my hair buns there and my uh ribbon.
I would call this ribbon. Ignore the whiskers but...
if you can ignore the whiskers. Those are not cat whiskers.
But it's cute! You can wear it, a cap!
Buy this cap. It's a good cap. No cap.
So cute.
Topi ya guys. Apalagi panas-panas.
It's a cap, guys. Especially when it's hot.
Harus pake topi nggak sih guys, panas-panas.
You have to wear a cap, right guys, when it's hot.
Apalagi silau gitu. Keren kalau pake topi lho guys.
Especially when it's glaring. It's cool if you wear a cap guys.
Terus keren lagi item gitu topinya.
Then it's cool again the cap is black.
Keren keren keren.
Cool cool cool.
まだあるのかな？うん。
Is there still more? Yeah.
あると思う。うん。じゃ、次、どうぞ。
I think there is. Yeah. Then, next, please.
Ugh...
I... uh...
It's so cute!
It's a... sleepy cat Zzz plushie.
It's called Sleepy Cat Zzz Plushie.
I know, but I swear it's not...
Okay, it's not... It's um...
If you notice, it's based on my Cat Day KV...
so it's so cute, right?
みんなあのCat Dayの時覚えてる？
Does everyone remember that Cat Day?
これ... this is the goods from last time.
This... this is the goods from last time.
It's so cute, right?
Look at those eyes!
It's so cute!
I wanna squish it and just...
jumble it up!
It's so cute!
And she's like sleeping because...
um, I heard that cats nap for 16 hours...
although that has nothing to do with me, I'm just saying.
It's very cute.
It's like sleeping. Mmm.
眠そう...
Sleepy...
眠そうゼータちゃん。
Sleepy Zeta-chan.
眠いゼータちゃん？可愛い！
Sleepy Zeta-chan? Cute!
Buy it! Or else...
or else... you don't wanna miss this,
because everyone liked the Cat Day KV...
You won't miss this.
Okay.
Even more... let's see.
Next please. 次！
Next please. Next!
お願いします！
Please!
Voice! Wah! Voice!
Voice... wah... Voice...
Voice, and it's titled 'A Fateful Meeting'.
Last but not least, there's also a bonus for who purchases the full set.
Okay. Full set...
Full setを買ってる人がボーナスもらえるぞ。
People who buy the full set get a bonus.
Okay, okay.
Kalian dapat bonus kalau kalian beli full set, okay?
You guys get a bonus if you buy the full set, okay?
Last one please.
最後お願いします！
One last time, please!
Ta-da! Here's the bonus!
Wah! It's the limited edition!
You'll get my signature.
Okay?
It's so good. It's like handwritten signature and all that.
Ugh, it's the best.
It's limited so get it now!
Limited... specialだよね？
Limited... it's special, right?
一番... うん、Special.
The most... yeah, Special.
Of course, it's a little ad break but we're not gonna stop there,
because I, even though it's my birthday, I want to give to you instead.
Yeah.
But it's not over yet.
これで終わりじゃないよ。
This isn't the end, you know.
It's my birthday, but I also want to give you a present as well. So...
Aren't you excited?
Okay.
Let's come get your present!
Woo!
Are you guys ready?
Going going my way もう放っといて
Going going my way, leave me alone already.
止めらんない熱身任せて
Unstoppable heat, leaving it to the body.
こりごりだRuleは Break it down
I'm sick of rules, break it down.
我慢できない Let me free
Can't hold back, let me free.
目が眩んでしまいそうな
Eyes about to be dazzled,
出で立ちのMermaid
Mermaid in that appearance.
黄昏てただけ But then
Just twilight, but then,
今は何も響かない
Now nothing resonates.
I know who I am, I...
Brandingには仮面
Mask for branding,
今は完全無視よNonsense
now completely ignoring it, Nonsense.
浴びのGreedy Style
Bathing in Greedy Style.
ダサい厄介も興味ないの
I have no interest in tacky troubles.
ありのまんまでいたい
I want to be just as I am.
Going going my way もう放っといて
Going going my way, leave me alone already.
止めらんない熱身任せて
Unstoppable heat, leaving it to the body.
こりごりだRuleは Break it down
I'm sick of rules, break it down.
我慢できない Let me free
Can't hold back, let me free.
We are special でしょ
We are special, right?
揺るがないPride
Unwavering Pride.
それだけでいいの
That's all I need.
タラレバだらけのLonely life
Lonely life full of 'what ifs'.
I feel Break it down. Break it.
We are special でしょ
We are special, right?
誰に言われても
No matter what anyone says,
私は歌うよ
I will sing.
Unfairばかりの世界など Break it down
Break down a world full of unfairness.
Break it 進め
Break it, move forward!
Break it down. Break it 進め
Break it down. Break it, move forward!
I just don't care about you
履いてくのMakeやFashion
Make-up and Fashion to put on.
雑音には構わないよ
I don't care about the noise.
この身と心、誰のものでもないでしょ
This body and heart don't belong to anyone, right?
いい加減いい大人だよね
You're a grown adult already, aren't you?
Ini wajah apa adanya
This face is as it is,
Tidak sempurna tapi sepenuhnya diriku
not perfect but fully myself.
でも今は楽しいよ
But now it's fun,
ありのまんまでいられるから
because I can be just as I am.
Going going my way もう放っといて
Going going my way, leave me alone already.
止めらんない熱身任せて
Unstoppable heat, leaving it to the body.
こりごりだRuleは Break it down
I'm sick of rules, break it down.
我慢できない Let me free
Can't hold back, let me free.
We are special でしょ
We are special, right?
揺るがないPride
Unwavering Pride.
それだけでいいの
That's all I need.
タラレバだらけのLonely life
Lonely life full of 'what ifs'.
I feel Break it down. Break it.
We are special でしょ
We are special, right?
誰に言われても
No matter what anyone says,
私は歌うよ
I will sing.
ありきたりな世界など Break it down
A mundane world like this, Break it down
Break it 進め
Break it, move forward
Can't break me down, breaking me
Break it down, break it down
Let's go! Break it down
Break it 進め
Break it, move forward
Break it down, break it down
Go! Goin' my way もう放っといて
Go! Goin' my way, leave me alone
止めらんない Destiny 任せて
Can't stop this destiny, leave it to me
こりごりだ Rule は Break it down
I'm sick of these rules, Break it down
我慢できない Let me free
I can't hold back, Let me free
Thank you everyone!
That was Break It Down!
Secretary! If you like it, make some noise! Whoa!
MISSION COMPLETE!
MY WORLD WOULD NOT BE
COMPLETE WITHOUT U,
SECRETARY!
YOUR SUPPORT MEANS
THE WORLD TO ME! :D
LET'S KEEP DOING MISSIONS
TOGETHER, FOREVER...
KEEP BREAKIN IT DOWN!